tabfu.com 2018-06-20

# Privacy and Policy - TabFu

  * This Privacy Policy sets out how we, Bleupage Ltd, collect, store and use information about you when you use or interact with our website, ultimate.bleupage.online and where we otherwise obtain or collect information about you. This Privacy Policy is effective from [25th May 2018].

  * Your privacy and protection of the information you share with us while using our Services are very important to us. This "Privacy Policy" explains what information we gather from our users and how we use it. By using or accessing our Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. (Capitalized terms not defined herein have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service). TabFu is not intended for children under 13 years of age. Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), we will never knowingly gather or use personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13, and we do not allow anyone under the age of 13 to register on TabFu.

  * What information do we collect? 

We collect and stores three types of information about users that are subject to our Privacy Policy:

    1. Information users provide to us:These are voluntary submissions made when creating an account on TabFu or through your use of the Services, such as name and email address, or payment information provided during purchases. Please understand that when you sign into TabFu or post or upload any content, your information is not anonymous to us.

    2. Information we collect when users interact with TabFu:We keep track of user interactions with our Services, such as visiting a web page, clicking a button, and choosing a form. Also, when users access our Services, we may collect information about their access method (such as hardware and software attributes), location, IP address, and pages they visit. In addition, we store certain information from their browser using "cookies". (For more on cookies, please see the section "What are cookies?")

    3. Information we receive from third parties:We do not own or operate any third-party services offered that you may use or interact with through our Services (collectively, "Third Party Services"). Whenever you visit, use or interact with a Third Party Service, we may receive information from them, including information about actions you take and Content you post on that service.

  * Why do we collect your information? 

TabFu collects information in order to improve the content and quality of our Services and to provide a customized experience tailored to your needs. Any personally identifiable information we collect (including email addresses, physical addresses or phone numbers) is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under special circumstances outlined in this Privacy Policy.

  * What are cookies?

TabFu may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. These cookies help us make TabFu easier to use, to make our advertising better, and to protect both you and TabFu. For example, a cookie may be used to store or "remember" your Member login information (but not your password) so that you are not required to manually log into the site at every visit. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases that may impact your ability to use some of our Services.

  * How secure is my information?

TabFu uses commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural measures to safeguard any information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. We limit access to personal information about you to employees whom we believe reasonably need that information to provide support, products, or services to you or to fulfill their roles within our organization. Although we have established and maintain security procedures to protect your personally identifiable information, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. You can reduce the risk of unauthorized access to your information by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up-to-date antivirus software. Please report any security violations to us on this automated form.

  * What control do I have over my information?

As a registered Member, you may modify or update your personal account information at any time by logging into your account. Should you desire to do so, you may also delete and close your TabFu account at any time by contacting our support team. Note that removed or deleted information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time.

  * How is information shared?

TabFu will not share your personally identifiable information with others except as described herein and in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is reasonably necessary to offer the Services, legally required, or permitted by you. For example, we may provide information to service providers to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business, such as to host the Services at a co-location facility for servers, to send out email updates about the Services, to remove repetitive information from our user lists, to process payments for products or services, or to provide search results or links (including sponsored links). In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the TabFu-specified purposes. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of TabFu (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary:

    1. To conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by TabFu, whether or not a response is required by applicable law.

    2. To enforce the TabFu Terms of Service or to protect our rights.

    3. To protect the safety or rights of members of the public or users of the Services.

TabFu reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of TabFu or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

  * How am I notified of changes to this Privacy Policy?

We may change this Privacy Policy pursuant to the procedures outlined in our Terms of Service. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information we have about you and your account. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by publication here.

  * Who can I contact about this Privacy Policy?

To submit an inquiry about our Privacy Policy, Please contact our [Support Department](mailto:support@tabfu.zendesk.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy).

  * Who can I contact about this Privacy Policy?

To submit an inquiry about our Privacy Policy, Please contact our [Support Department](mailto:support@tabfu.zendesk.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy).

  * Cookie

Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. We may also automatically record certain information from your device by using various types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This automatically collected information may include your IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use the Service, the pages or other content you view or otherwise interact with on the Service, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the Service. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding your interaction with email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message, to the extent permitted under applicable law. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Service to their fullest potential.

  *   * Browser settings

You can accept or reject some or all cookies (for example, blocking all third party cookies) by adjusting your browser settings. If you do not know how to do this, the links below set out information about how to change your browser settings for some of the most commonly used web browsers: \- Google Chrome: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en-GB \- Mozilla Firefox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-browsing-search-download-history-firefox?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Clear+Recent+History \- Microsoft Internet Explorer: https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/278835/how-to-delete-cookie-files-in-internet-explorer \- Apple Safari: https://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042?locale=en_US Some browsers, such as Chrome and Firefox, allow you to change your settings to browse in ‘incognito’ mode, limiting the amount of data placed on your machine and automatically deleting any persistent cookies placed on your device when you finish your browsing session. There are also many third party applications which you can add to your browser to block or manage cookies.
